+ TOP MENU

* Internet

* TV Service

Privacy Policy
==============

Version 1.0

_Last revised on: April 25, 2018_

We take the privacy and protection of personal information very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding the Personal Data (as defined below) we collect from users of the AEBC website at aebc.com (the “Site”) and the services made available through the Site provided by AEBC Internet Corp. (“AEBC”, “us”, “our”, and “we”).

### User Consent

By submitting Personal Data through our Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### A Note about Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Data from visitors who are under the age of 13.

A Note to Users Outside of the United States

Your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

### Types of Data We Collect

“Personal Data” means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. “Anonymous Data” means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below.

### Information You Provide to Us

When you create an account (“Account”) to register for the Forum, we will collect your username, e-mail address and password. We may also collect optional information that you provide us to customize your Account, for example, your language preference, location, time zone, birthdates, occupation, interests, instant messenger ID and website.

When you post a comment on the Site, we will collect your username and e-mail address and, if you provide it, your website.

When you post comments or messages to the Site, the information contained in your posting will be stored on our servers and other users will be able to see it.

We retain information on your behalf, such as your postings to the Site and files and messages that you store using your Account.

If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply.

When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information.

We also collect other types of Personal Data that you provide to us voluntarily, such as your operating system and version, product registration number, and other requested information if you contact us via e-mail regarding support for the Services.

We may also collect Personal Data, such as at other points in our Services that state that Personal Data is being collected.

### Information Collected via Technology

**Information Collected by Our Servers**. To make our Services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, referring/exit pages, clickstream data (including the ads you see and click on), and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the Services, track users’ movements around the Site, gather demographic information about our user base as a whole, and better tailor our Services to our users’ needs. For example, some of the information may be collected so that when you visit the Site again, it will recognize you and the information could then be used by us to serve advertisements and other information appropriate to your interests. Except as noted in this Privacy Policy, we do not link this automatically-collected data to Personal Data.

**Cookies.** We store small text files called “Cookies” on your computer to make your experience on our website better. We use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). In order to provide the Services, we use a variety of Cookies that perform different functions. While you will still be able to use the AEBC Internet Corp Offerings if you disable Cookies in your browser, certain parts of the AEBC Internet Corp Offerings may not function as effectively. You can find more information on Cookies and how they may affect you by visiting: [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). We use the following types of cookies:

**_Strictly Necessary Cookies_**. Strictly necessary cookies are cookies which are essential to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies, services you have asked for cannot be provided.

**_Performance Cookies_**. Performance cookies collect anonymized information about how you use our website. For example, these cookies may tell us which pages you go to most often and if you receive error messages from our webpages. We use this information to improve how our sites work. By using our web site, you agree we can place these cookies on your device.

**_Functionality Cookies_**. Functionality Cookies allow our website to remember the choices you make, such as your login information (if any), preferred language or region you are in, and can provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. By using our web site, you agree we can place these cookies on your device.

**_Advertising Cookies_**. These cookies collect information to deliver you more relevant advertising. They may be placed by us, by third parties acting on our behalf, or by advertising networks with our permission. They remember other websites you have visited, and advertising networks may share this information with others including advertisers. By using our web site, you agree we can place these cookies on your device.

**Tracking Pixels**. In addition, we use “Tracking Pixels,” which are small transparent graphic image (usually only 1 pixel) that we place on our Site that is used to collect information about the pages you view and when you view them.

**Google Analytics**. We use Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the Site. Google Analytics uses Cookies to collect information such as how often users visit the Site, what pages they visit, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our Site and Services. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Site, rather than your name or other personally identifying information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.

### Use of Your Personal Data

#### **General Use**

In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. We use your Personal Data in the following ways:

Provide the Services you request;

Facilitate the creation of and secure your Account on our network;

Identify you as a user in our system;

Provide improved administration of our Services;

Improve the quality of experience when you interact with our Services;

Send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your Account was created;

Send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories;

to send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to our Services and for other marketing purposes of AEBC Internet Corp if you elect to receive them.

#### Creation of Anonymous Data

We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content and navigation of our Services. We reserve the right to use Anonymous Data for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties in its sole discretion.

#### Disclosure of Your Personal Data

We disclose your Personal Data as described below and as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

#### Third Party Service Providers

We may share your Personal Data with our third party service providers to provide you with the Services. These third party service providers are required not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by us.

#### Affiliates and Acquisitions

We may share some or all of your Personal Data with our parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (“Affiliates”), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Other Disclosures

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), we may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary (a) in connection with any legal investigation; (b) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; (c) to protect or defend our rights or property or users of the Services; and/or (d) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or Terms of Use.

#### Third Party Websites

When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Services and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites.

#### Public Content

When you post reviews, comments, or messages to the Services, we will display such content along with your username on the Services. Once displayed on publicly viewable web pages, that information can be read, collected and used by other registered or unregistered users of the Services. We cannot control who reads your comments or messages or what other users may do with the information that you voluntarily post.

### Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Data

#### Choices

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Data.

We will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our Services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below).

Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service related communication, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to Personal Data

You may change any of your Personal Data in your Account by editing your profile within your Account. You may request deletion of your Personal Data by us, but please note that we may be required to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. We may retain your information for fraud prevention or similar purposes.

#### Security of Your Personal Data

We are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Data. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We also require you to enter a password to access your Account information. Please do not disclose your Account password to unauthorized people. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Contact Information

We welcome your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please e-mail us at legal@aebc.com.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Services. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earliest of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Services. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Service. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Data to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your Account with us. Continued use of our Service, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

www.aebc.com reserves the right to change this policy. If we do make changes, the revised privacy policy will be posted on this site.

### How to Contact Us

You may contact us via the following methods:

Address:  
B11-970 Burrard Street  
Vancouver, BC, Canada  
V6Z 2R4

Sales: 604-288-1088

Support: 604-288-1089

We take your privacy and security seriously.

#### AEBC Contact Info

**AEBC Internet Corporation**

B11 - 970 Burrard Street  
Vancouver, B.C, Canada, V6Z 2R4

**Phone** 604-288-1088

**Fax** 604-628-0747

**Email [](mailto:cs@aebc.com)** [cs@aebc.com](mailto:cs@aebc.com)

**Office Hours:**  
Monday to Friday 9:00AM to 5:30PM  
Pick-up during these hours only

Call us if you have questions on access  
**604-288-1088** for assistance.

Building Access Instructions

×

Building Access Instructions
----------------------------

* 1\. In the lobby of our 970 Burrard St. building, please use the right hand side elevator to reach level B (left elevator does not reach level B)
* 2\. If the right hand elevator is unavailable, please call our office so we may assist you further.
* 3\. Please note our office hours are M-F 9:00am - 5:30pm

#### AEBC Latest News and Updates

* [Is Business Fibre Optic Internet Worth the Price? Unleashing the Power of Speed](https://www.aebc.com/articles/business-fibre-optic-internet-worth-price-unleashing-power-speed/)
* [10 Tips and Tricks to Optimize Your Internet Speed and Improve Your Online Experience](https://www.aebc.com/articles/10-tips-tricks-optimize-internet-speed-improve-online-experience/)
* [Switch to AEBC Fibre Internet and Get More of What You Really Want](https://www.aebc.com/articles/switch-aebc-fibre-internet-get-really-want/)

AEBC Sales Team

**Call [604-288-8388](tel:6042888388)**

Mon-Fri from 9:30am - 5:30pm

sales@aebc.com

Order AEBC Internet Online:

Need Technical Support?

**Call [604-288-1089](tel:6042881089)**

Mon-Fri from 8:30am – 11:30pm

tss@aebc.com

©2024 AEBC Internet Corp - Connecting the Future.

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.[Accept](#) [Read More](https://www.aebc.com/privacy-policy/)

Privacy & Cookies Policy

* [](# "Chinese (Simplified)")
* [](# "Chinese (Traditional)")
